{
    "id": "55553250fcf847a09ebccec199539f44",
    "title": "Since And For",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been associated with this institution …………….. ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been ailing ……………… November.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. when have you been attending the course?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "These foreigners have been learning Sanskrit ………………… six months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister has been learning music ………………. last January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has worked as a peon ……………. ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known Kumar ……………. two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known Kumar …………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been teaching yoga …………….. three years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. when have you been learning music ?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}